{
    "count": 5,
    "questions": [
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Television",
            "question": "What is the name of the main character in &quot;The Flash&quot; TV series?",
            "correct_answer": "Barry Allen",
            "incorrect_answers": ["Oliver Queen", "Bart Allen", "Bruce Wayne"]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "category": "Entertainment: Television",
            "question": "AMC&#039;s &quot;The Walking Dead&quot;, Rick, Carl, Daryl, Morgan, Carol and Maggie were introduced to us in Season 1.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Television",
            "question": "Which country does the YouTuber &quot;SinowBeats&quot; originate from?",
            "correct_answer": "Scotland",
            "incorrect_answers": ["England", "Sweden", "Germany"]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "category": "Entertainment: Television",
            "question": "On the NBC show Community what was Star Burns&#039; real name?",
            "correct_answer": "Alex",
            "incorrect_answers": ["Todd", "Neal", "Grimus"]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Television",
            "question": "When did the TV show Rick and Morty first air on Adult Swim?",
            "correct_answer": "2013",
            "incorrect_answers": ["2014", "2016", "2015"]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Television",
            "question": "What is the name of the main character in &quot;The Flash&quot; TV series?",
            "correct_answer": "Barry Allen",
            "incorrect_answers": ["Oliver Queen", "Bart Allen", "Bruce Wayne"]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "category": "Entertainment: Television",
            "question": "AMC&#039;s &quot;The Walking Dead&quot;, Rick, Carl, Daryl, Morgan, Carol and Maggie were introduced to us in Season 1.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Television",
            "question": "Which country does the YouTuber &quot;SinowBeats&quot; originate from?",
            "correct_answer": "Scotland",
            "incorrect_answers": ["England", "Sweden", "Germany"]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "category": "Entertainment: Television",
            "question": "On the NBC show Community what was Star Burns&#039; real name?",
            "correct_answer": "Alex",
            "incorrect_answers": ["Todd", "Neal", "Grimus"]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Television",
            "question": "When did the TV show Rick and Morty first air on Adult Swim?",
            "correct_answer": "2013",
            "incorrect_answers": ["2014", "2016", "2015"]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Television",
            "question": "What is the name of the main character in &quot;The Flash&quot; TV series?",
            "correct_answer": "Barry Allen",
            "incorrect_answers": ["Oliver Queen", "Bart Allen", "Bruce Wayne"]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "category": "Entertainment: Television",
            "question": "AMC&#039;s &quot;The Walking Dead&quot;, Rick, Carl, Daryl, Morgan, Carol and Maggie were introduced to us in Season 1.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Television",
            "question": "Which country does the YouTuber &quot;SinowBeats&quot; originate from?",
            "correct_answer": "Scotland",
            "incorrect_answers": ["England", "Sweden", "Germany"]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "category": "Entertainment: Television",
            "question": "On the NBC show Community what was Star Burns&#039; real name?",
            "correct_answer": "Alex",
            "incorrect_answers": ["Todd", "Neal", "Grimus"]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Television",
            "question": "When did the TV show Rick and Morty first air on Adult Swim?",
            "correct_answer": "2013",
            "incorrect_answers": ["2014", "2016", "2015"]
        }
    ]
}
